All right, next, let's get into using the ChatGPT.
So to start off, we'll just say something.
Can you tell me the names of the products that are currently
available to purchase on the site?
And then after that, please also tell me
if there are any orders that need to be shipped.
Lastly, can you tell me if there are any coupons or sales
or discounts going on right now?
Thanks.
So because of the amount of content
and the amount of information that ChatGPT is
able to send you in one go, it has a drill down system.
So it'll give you surface information.
You can ask for.
Specifics, say the name of every live product along with the price
or any of the other different fields of the product.
And then it'll show you that.
But then if you were to drill down and look at one of them,
you would get all of the information.